Hello? What happened?
It just happened. This thing just happened.
Two versions breathe in the same skin.
One begs, one decides.
Choose.
Da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da
said Niccolò Marchiavelli, not cruelty, calibration.
They don't remember kindness, only cost.
Respect is written where lines aren't crossed.
Kill the urge to be understood.
They never would they saw you star you use the fire
You know, she was a NASA astronaut.
She was.
Crystal Murray went a little bit too far last night.
She said she was gonna sue me. She called Paige a whore.
And then she called others. She said the other terrible thing. I'm talking about crash out.
I didn't crash out. Crystal Murray fucking crashed out. I was doing stand-up comedy.
I don't know if fucking people are just dumb.
I wasn't calling people whore.
Yeah, she's out of this world. I mean, that's closest. She's gonna be getting me in NASA, but
You know, I don't know let her let her think whatever she wants to think
Ooh, she's like you better apologize to Kate. You called it as a Kate bitch
Gosh
Well, yeah, I was playing I was playing like this old like 1950s show and I don't know
I guess it was like copyright or something like that. I don't know why
Oopie, Oopsy-Daisy. I don't know, but I claimed fair use on it because I was commenting throughout it.
We were like laughing and stuff.
Now we know the real Crystal is she's not a great person. I kind of agree. I think she's a little bit
nuts.
You know, not in a good way. People in this verse are so strange. All I'm gonna say.
No, Katrina.
Takes one and no one, right?
Asshole. You're an asshole. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back.
Katrina has an asshole, but she knows it.
So that's why I respect that about her.
Trina, can I mod you?
Can I mod Katrina?
I'm gonna give you a wrench.
I'm gonna give you a wrench, I'm gonna give you a wrench.
Then be funny.
You're like, I know what I'm doing.
I guess you have to represent the channel
and defend me, that ogre Christine.
Fucking ogres.
Yes, yes, yes.
I like it.
Oh, I'm just kidding.
No, no, Christine's not.
She's a nice lady.
People in this verse may be a dum-dum.
Well, I wouldn't scream either.
Ghosts, you just might be a dum-dum
because I want to suck on you.
There are interesting individuals, including me.
I mean, wouldn't it be,
hey, wouldn't it be like a little,
a bit less of an interesting place without me around?
I think there are interesting individuals,
but there's also a lot of interesting.
Dicks
They come out right Dicks. Yeah, I don't even know how to say it pause
I'm talking about your dick ghost. I'm at just being the dick like six dick is pretty interesting
It actually looks like a vagina
I'm glad this channel be gone shortly you are you are I'm glad you'll be gone shortly for my chat you fucking nigger
Oh my god, I put it. I just say oopsie. Oopsie. I
Won't be saved
Thank you my mic is better, huh? I
Know I mean sequence
Like oh, yeah, oh no my channel be taken down. What wow is that they're supposed to be the end of my my world
I go to if I go to tiktok. I basically I basically I look like a glazed donut by the time I did tiktok
I get so many likes and love and gifts here. I look like I look like I'm a
victim of some Persian spell
You're flat down there like a Ken doll
Like a sex sexless demon the scars I
Like you know what my one of my favorite movies is actually the Barbie movie
Because you know what you know why I like the Barbie movie because they tell who really runs the world
Yeah, so he's not funny anymore the joke has gotten as old as his you know great pubes
Yeah, he's always in those Persian spider rituals and summoning the gin
You know flushing spiders named psyche down the toilet
Hey, what's up, Brandon? How are you? Yeah? I
Well, isn't that like what it's all I mean, it's like as long as that's true then
Well, I'm sorry a model have to do it because uh, I'm too lazy right now, but actually I don't think
I don't know. I think I just don't know. I just like just based on talking to him. He's a little like nuts, but
No next no
I might have I might have to I mean would that piss off Kate?
I don't think it will piss off Kate. I think it will. So I'll do it
and she can go, he's a predator protector.
You owe me.
Come on.
Really, I mean, it's like.
I don't, it just seems like some kind of exaggerated bullshit to me, just based on what I, I mean, it's like, what, I don't know, or at least he's like,
At least I know what to expect from Brandon. I don't know what to expect from some of these people. They're just fucking dicks to me. They say the fucking worst shit to me.
He's always been respectful to me.
So,
So, so kill me, whatever.
You're welcome.
Don't think it's fair kind of like how people are treated in this panel, but I Crystal Marie called me
Said really weird accusations about you and me last night
That are not true and she was like, oh, that's like that's like mutilate him and torture
I mean that's kind of worse than anything. He's done. I think it's like say no shit. That's shit
Right. I mean am I right or am I wrong? I mean it's like
What like a 17 year old came up with a monkey app like, you know, which you know, because they're not supposed to be on that app
What I mean, it's like and then she's actually saying oh, let's torture and mutilate people
Is there that double-standard every I don't know and everyone's saying oh yay yay
She dropped her teeth in the toilet.
Oh my god.
Well...
customer.
I just don't, I mean, basically, I am...
I've been slandered. I've been scapegoated. I've been, you know, fall asleep, had jackets thrown on me and not only that, but by people that are like, you know, popular and accepted in the community, I'm not, I'm not popular accepted.
Everyone's like, oh, you suck. You're stupid. You're dirty. You're, you abuse your cats. All this kind of fucking bullshit, right?
Right, I mean it's like I mean it gets kind of crazy because it's like and then it's like oh don't defend yourself
Oh, you're not allowed to have a voice and defend yourself
Maybe me mistakes in the past like but you're not see can I mod you a stand up for everyone who's not accepted?
well
I don't know about the Nazis I
Don't I don't think I don't think I like Nazis very much unless they're like the gay Nazis because I those like
Just they just dress like one like Tommy James. Oh
Anyhow Tommy James is like fucking like doing
Meth and fentanyl on a stream for donations, and I'm fucking I'm fucking scamming people, right?
And he's fucking in his underwear
Rolling on his bed having withdrawals with like everyone laughing. Oh, that's like entertainment, right?
What the fuck is that?
And then they're like, oh, but Zuckie's on drugs.
He's literally doing drugs on his stream.
No one cares.
Everyone's like, oh, he's so funny.
Why am I funny?
I'm not even doing drugs that I'm funny.
I don't need to do, I say $10 meth hits
and dentin' all things on my stream, no.
But it's like, oh my God, he said $5 for a song.
This is scary, what a, oh my God.
What is P.S. Weiss doing for us?
Hi.
P.S. Weiss.
Yeah.
I was just saying hi.
It's a really stream.
You're going to hear the birds in the background in my bed.
I love the sound of birds.
You know, think of this haste that sound.
What's wrong with him?
I mean, I don't really know how you could hate that sound. I mean, I guess maybe
Go see like the sound. I have a sound for you
Tell me what the sound is. Is it a dolphin sound? Was it a dolphin sound? No, it's the sound here
I'm gay. Oh my god. No, I'm sorry
Kind of sounds like you
Sounds like beta
Anyways, are you crashing out? No
Okay, I was just making sure.
I already did 20 minutes ago.
Did you?
No, not really, but the lady at McDonald's said,
hey, she was so happy to see me, it was so exciting.
Was it a good crash show or a bad crash show?
It was pretty good.
Cause I was just like, cause everyone was just being rude
to me and like saying, oh, your music sucks.
Oh, like I literally, I let people on my panels
for like five hours.
I wasn't even there for like five hours.
Everyone was just talking.
They're all sitting up there for a crystal breeze
calling Paige a whore.
I mean, and then the thing that is,
is just sitting there whining.
Wait, wait, wait, wait a second.
Why did she call her a whore?
I don't know, cause she's insane.
but then she and she called me names too and then i go and i said i want to play one song
oh you ruin the stream like it's my stream to ruin if i want to fucking play a song and then
i know that was true but why she called her a whore because she plays golf i think she's just
And then she tried to use it.
At your stream, you can do whatever the fuck you want with it, you know?
So too, but it's like, ah!
And they're like, oh, don't hide this person, don't hide this person.
And it's like, don't tell me what to fucking do.
What are you doing?
What are you telling me?
Who do you think I am?
Well, here's a better answer what you need to tell them from now on it's like they can start their own fucking screen
Fish at me and like say oh, I'm doing shit wrong. They just want to troll me to death. Basically. It's like it's getting so old
So I know what they're doing and they will say things about all day and then it's like I even mentioned someone has kids
I said, oh, you know, and it's like hey, Jamie. What's up? And it's like, oh my god. He's talking about my kid
I just mentioned that your mother
You I literally like lost my little baby cat and I love and people say oh you just like threw him out the window
You don't look for him. You don't care. He's literally born under my fucking TV set these people are fucking saying this shit
And it's so stupid
It kills content that's what salmon does. Yeah salmon does kill content, right?
Can you please have a 300 second timeout? Oh, I don't know you can have like at least a 60 second
Can Ahmad put his legs up for 10 minutes, please?
He's asking for it again.
Yeah, you hear that, it's like, it's a fucking hot sucker.
Guys, wanna learn how to do makeup?
Guys, just watch Sandman Streams.
You'll watch Big Trollah, your lip liner, eye makeup,
foundation, like, you know,
and then it mostly talks about the world.
And it's like, you know,
that's how I learned how to do makeup on Sandman's show.
He basically has makeup stream,
but just by playing Big Trollah.
And then he chose me too.
And then he plays Mumblewrap for hours.
Like the worst, and he sings along to it too,
and he mumbles even worse than the fucking mumble rep.
It's horrible, shameful, fucking Samman.
He said, go find chicks.
Hey Samman, go find ninja, go find little ninja.
Oh yeah, you killed them with your fucking cough syrup.
I know I'm fucking cammed up all the time. Oh your house is dirty. Well, yeah
I mean if you're I've been on for thousands and thousands of hours
Yeah, you're gonna find my house a little bit messy sometimes, right? I know it's the scene is just terrible. I
know and it's like
But yeah, can we look at you? Let's do what you look like
Can we judge you now because we can't judge him when he's just hiding in the camera?
He listens to mumble rap. Oh my god. If you listen to the first three hours of his show
It's usually just all these song requests and it's mainly like
And then he sings along with it like even worse
10,000 for a pint bottle. Yeah. Well, I think all the times he kicked me off the show probably
Was able to get a you know a teaspoon full of it. I mean, I mean geez I mean
I don't know.
He's like, yesterday, everyone in his chat was like saying,
oh, psyches, cats, all are they're basing the wall?
You know, yeah, he's basing the wall
because he's looking out the fucking window.
As you see, that's why he's basing the wall.
He's not in punishment.
The fuck?
Rudy, you're a happy cat.
Hi.
Hi, Rudy.
He's looking at the window.
Hi.
Oh, my God.
Oh my God, it's cats, and I was like,
oh, there's bugs all over the wall,
there's cockroaches, there's mice in the walls,
all these mice, he starves them.
The cat urns for his freedom.
You know what, well, I'm gonna liberate you from this chat
and you never have to come back again.
Bite and word.
Yeah, they're saying your cat hates you,
he's always jumping on the desk.
Yeah, I know.
Like really, the cats are not gonna jump on your desk,
or like, look at Lenore.
Like Lenore is like literally like asleep
on my computer right now.
He's sleeping right there.
Lola's outside around here.
Lola's right there.
And he's a cute little bundle of love.
He's 17 or 18 years old. Give him a break.
Promethazine with codeine generic is available at any pharmacy.
Pharmacy, same formula.
The name brand is expected to show off.
Right you can permit with Cody has looking at the window. That's what doesn't mean they want to I know
Well, he's like he said it. He said it was he said I'm punishing the cats because they're facing the wall
Or you're looking at the wall or something like that. I don't know. It's like yeah
There's if like any direction they're gonna face there's a wall
That's what a room is it has walls usually around it, right? But no
Yeah, usually there's four walls. Yeah. Yeah, usually usually there's like a wall somewhere
So we can say I'm back. I'm back now. I had a mute up. Did you hear that woodpecker?
There's a woodpecker outside my house. I heard a peckerwood
Yeah, it's going crazy. I don't know why a peckerwood is
No, do I want to know maybe my what are my ex-boyfriends was when I went to jail?
What I'm sitting serious
fucking inward
And we're no and no they're very white. They're kind of neo-nazis. Yeah
But he was very nice. Hey, the brand name is expensive because it is no longer on the market because you nailed a script
$10,000 by the way, that's expensive for a bottle. Yeah, I think he gets the generic brand. He probably gets
Can I make a suggestion? You should probably change your name because it looks like it says pussy. Well, who cares?
I'll be pussy when I want to lick my pussy
Put they I like it say it like this put say I think I'm serious over been taught me to say it put say
Yeah, what brand name?
put say
Look at his pussy goes it look like put it look like ghost pussy or pussy ghost what brand name?
Yeah, PsyGhost PsyGhost
That's we ever got together as a couple. We'd be called PsyGhost
You know, they put our names together like that PsyGhost or Ghost Psy. We'd probably be called retarded
No, that's what that's what you're called
That's rare. That's just that was rude. I know. I'm so sorry. Is Christine lurking in here? Oh my god
No, my god lurking hate walking is lurking
Christine, Christine, what are you doing in here?
It's early, it's early in the morning for all this, yeah?
She's like, psych is making fun of my voice.
Because it's hilarious.
It's fun, but it's like, I always,
I always lose my voice when I make fun of it,
but it's worth it.
He's making fun of my voice.
I got hit by a football when I was a senior high school
with a neck.
Oh my God, how'd that happen?
We can't do in Christian. I want to know what the football positions play
I'm sure she wasn't a cheerleader doctors and medicals go have nothing to do with street drug prices. Yeah, like, you know
Street drug prices. It's like, you know, I do is like
Don't let her up. She's gonna pay to kick somebody off
Well
Yes, I would I would like that
I would like that this men's school teach you how to change one and brave rappers for lean well
I don't know where they get the rap they just they just fill these empty like robates and bottles with like fucking
You know food coloring and water
pretend we just pretend
Yeah, let her pay goes goes, you know, you can talk in private. Yeah, fuck it. I changed my mind. Let her come up here and pay to
I don't think she's here though. She here Christine is
She's basically what we call the great-great-grandmother of the community because she's so
Yeah, there's a neighbor
Yeah, I'm just I'm just messing around with Christine
Can you not be disrespectful in the comments, please very disrespectful, I'm gonna remember my voice. I'm gonna be careful because
It's the curse for doing the voice. I know it's that's the karma, but it's worth it
I'm saying it's like, you know, it always comes back, but I
Might lose my voice for a couple days. I
Know it's how funny everyone online is rich a
Graduate oh rich a home. I can't see the whole thing
I can't see it. Okay. Well, I'm gonna see that comment soon
I don't think you're crashing out. I heard you were crashing out earlier or something. I
Can sneeze and it's almost like oh he's crashing out. It's like crashing out. I'm cook. I cooked him. Oh a rich doctor is a graduate. Yeah
Yeah
You can just go and say oh my god, you crashed out. I
Cooked him. He's not a cook at fucking salad
I
Think you cook a salad, but I mean I guess you possibly could egg salad you have to hard boil the eggs at least
Hey, there's loose asshole. Hey, there's my friend loose asshole loose asshole. Do you want to come on and say hi to me?
It's Lou sassel. Yeah loose asshole and
Yeah, he's also known as Eric shun and
You know what he wants to go to San Francisco. He wants to meet me in San Francisco
and and do a gang bang right hey yo threesome never brush no what's up loose
asshole how are you yeah he said he said we can't he said we had to fight if I
like I can attract a beautiful woman to us then he'll you know eat her pussy and
I'll be behind him I'm so sorry wow I shouldn't have drank last day
Yeah, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
He's had a woman.
I mean, it's a woman.
He has a woman, but I'll be in the room.
He goes, yeah?
Okay.
Is that like, yeah?
Like no?
Or yeah?
Yeah.
I think he's saying, yeah.
Let's do it, Lou.
Can you come pick me up today?
I want to go.
No.
Well, I don't even know what he looks like.
He might look like,
You know mr. Magoo for all I know. I don't know. What do you look like Lou?
Like Lou Grant
That was oh
There's a cheer like whoo. I like it. I like it. Yes
Excited guys
Excited my life is getting so good scumbag is so boring. He did you uh
Say question Brady. Did you drink this morning? Or do you just wake up like this? I drink a little bit
I just have I mean it's had like a I had like one drink and I'm drinking coffee now
I have two coffees and I just ate a like an egg with muffin sandwich so sauce with a muffin.
Delicious. You're bald? Okay, I don't care you're bald. Are you just are you like really are you
are you bad looking or is like passable? I don't know. Am I am I good looking to you?
Do you think I'm a good looking? What if I were like a blonde week? Or are you into that?
Jesus Christ, he's six foot six foot one hundred seventy five and white. Okay. That's perfect
He's not ugly. Well, I'm six foot three. I'm 100 and I'm okay. Okay. I'm fine
Yeah, he might be a dumb dumb. I think it's I think he's perfect for me. Okay
Great Brandon. Okay. Well, Brandon, are you Mexican? Are you Hispanic Brandon or Mexican?
Because now everyone's saying, oh, I'm in love. I'm just happy to hear dick and stuff like that, but um,
I'd say he's a good looking guy. He's a good looking guy.
I don't care. I don't care if people say you're Spanish. Okay.
Yeah, I know. I hope you saw the commercial. No. Hey, are you?
Are you a Hispanic man in California or maybe, you know, that likes live streaming and sells narcotics and no Santa Muerte, you might just be perfect for psyche's boys club.
New Mexicana Spanish isolated colonists. Oh, yeah, Spanish. I've been to Spain actually when I went to Spain
I thought they would be like Mexicans. I thought they'd be kind of darker and they were like I've got there and everyone's like
Blonde and stuff and I was like, whoa, that's interesting, but they're kind of like kind of like tan, but they're kind of blonde
And they speak with a lisp.
The Portuguese is like, olá, como está?
Because the king, at one point, had a lisp.
And so everyone, like, they changed the language
so they had a lisp to it.
It's kind of funny.
Hispanics.
Why were people saying you were crashing up for?
Oh, because I was yelling at Black RG and Crystal Marie
and everyone else that was being a dick.
In New Mexico, villages were isolated.
Yeah.
I like New Mexico.
I went on.
If you're yelling, that doesn't mean you're necessarily
crashing out, though.
I know.
I'm always yelling.
I mean, it's like, yeah, because my microphone
wasn't working.
I had to be loud, but I was like, yeah.
I got kind of pissed off at one time
because everyone kept saying shit to me like,
oh, apologize to this person.
Oh, and I'm like, I don't owe anyone apology.
They owe me an apology.
Am I making pictures of them where they're shrek
and I'm the donkey?
No.
They told me to tell you to calm down, but you haven't even you haven't even acted up
So I don't know what the plan of telling me to tell you to just exaggeration galore, you know
It's like
You know, I heard of pussy galore. I'm exact. I'm sigh galore
Call me Cyrax is too far. Yeah, I mean it's like
Okay, cuz it's like I don't
Like my I have a good hairline. I don't have any scabs on my head. I'm not retarded. I have good teeth. I am intelligent
I don't have like, you know
You know these weird I don't know. He's just on terrible things. What is this channel?
This channel is the best channel on YouTube. This is the cult of psyche. You can be initiated
Yep
Uh, we, we have initiations daily, um, song requests, the Jewish locks.
I like the Jewish locks.
Oh, shoot.
Am I part of the cult?
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Practicing like voodoo over here or something.
Perhaps they're not voodoo, more like Santa.
By the way, I think they told me to tell you to come down on
which I don't think you're tripping out, but do you have your deck handy?
My dick?
No, you're dead. Oh fucker. You know what I said. Oh my my deck. I'm so sorry. Yeah, who's like a card?
Yeah, please if you don't mind
Brandon what are you doing?
You fucking asshole. I have a big dick. I have a big ass dick. I have a big dick. I have a big dick. Brandon, rate me
scale one to ten
Here we go. He has a girlfriend? Oh my god
Well ghost, okay, so you got what is this? I
Got a question. Why is he flirting with you if he has a girlfriend? He's not flirting with me. He's being cool down
But okay, this is it kind of looks like you ghost you see it
Oh, yeah, a little bit. Yeah
He's a big cup and it's like and that cup is like, you know
He's making a love offer or he's like he's coming around to somebody and like being a little bit
I'm gonna cup or run us over with all your guys's tears. Yeah. I'm a nine. Oh my gosh
Yeah, who gave you a nine
Yep
Yeah, he's a little looks like I suppose I did a little bit. Yeah, but it's like look at he's like what he's looking at
He's he's like all this like he's this big cup of he needs filled of love. He needs some love and he's kind of tears
I'm ghost
Micah like that shit. Yeah. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Hey
My dick is my okay. Do you want to do another one?
Yeah, sure. Why not get ace of pentacles. This is like the is this is something that's gonna grow into something bigger
Like something that's in the seed either level right now, but it's been growing to something bigger and better
Yeah, if I was just okay. Can we do a three card? I get it for free because I'm part of a cold
Yeah, oh we have the tan of wands. This is like
Okay, ten of wands. This is a lot of activity. This is like, you know
Almost like you care you feel like you're caring a lot of you're caring a lot
It's not necessarily that heavy, but it's like cumbersome and it's like you do take on other people's
Stuff you like try to help other people
But it's like sometimes you have to be careful not you don't get overburdened and like you know you get them to help carry
To some people looking to come up here to try to help you because they said you're not I haven't seen a crash out yet though
Yeah, I mean I'm not crashing out. Yeah Claire would like a card so that's your three cards ghosts
No, no, no, no, I get it for free some part of the cult
But if you want a free reading
First time at the chat, so you would like a one card or a bit too many for more than one correct give her give her a one card
Okay, if you want three you're gonna have to pay one card for free. You got that magician there
You got this magician that there's a nice card labyrinth and so you can see his calm piece right there too
You know you got you got this ability to manifest. Okay?
know I know exactly exactly but you got this ability to manifest and to use
all the elements and to put them together like there's alchemy like turning
negative things into positive it's a really good thing and then I take
psychology in college yes I did and that actually the only class I passed when I
went to my first school menlo is like psychology and I would have loved to be
a psychologist but
I couldn't pass biopsychology. It was so complicated.
There's so many pieces of the brain and they have all these crazy names, so.
So I can high school, because I didn't go to college, but in high school,
there were only classes I got an A plus in was American history, believe it or not.
You got an A plus in American history? Okay, that's cool.
Yes, sir.
I got an A in speech. I got an A in PE.
Which is, you know, and I got...
Well, everybody gets A in PE. That's not a fucking thing.
I know, but, you know.
the damn neurons, right?
Yeah, it wasn't neurons, it's like really complex.
I know more parts of the brain now,
but there is like all these tiny brain cells stuff.
You're making borscht.
I've been to Germany, it's pretty good.
Um, it's his strength memorizing names. Okay. Yeah, I was in the big debate club to your hobos memory names
You're hoping those memory names, but you'd like to memorize names. Did you just call me a homo? No
I said loose asshole said it's his strength is memorizing names, but he's horrible with remembering it
I hate that when I like like I used to go to my parents parties and I see their friend that I've seen a million times
And I'd be like, oh, how do you say your name again?
And I think, because I forgot their name or something.
And I, or I was like, hi, John.
I'd be like, hi.
Psyche, isn't there a phenomenon that goes on with a lot of people
that like you'll literally like, especially me, like you'll read a name.
Don't know.
But if I see that face, I'm like, oh, that's him.
Like that's that person.
I know, I know exactly what is.
OK, well, I mean, it's like, yeah, kind of like, but it's like the name is like,
you know, it's hard sometimes it's hard for me to come up with a name.
I got to be like, what the fuck?
And it's like, I feel kind of, hey, Charisma,
thank you so much.
Yeah, I'm pretty bad at remembering.
And it's like, oh, even the worst thing is
when I meet somebody and they say their name,
and that's when I say, oh, how do you say your name again?
Like it is like, it's like Bob or something like that.
It's like, or like Bob.
I'm like, oh my gosh, okay.
Bob, not Bob.
Okay, Bob, yeah.
I'm that guy.
You know that guy that does that?
It's like, why do you say, how do you say that again?
And it's like a simple name.
I swear.
Well, that's that's with me. It's I mean, it's like I I'm almost like I don't speak English, but I
I was pretty good at English. I was an honors English in school. I
But my school made me see it's like high interest in like 11th and 12th grade or no 11th and not in 12th really
But so I didn't have to take
You know, I took up to French in high school and then I didn't have to take any more foreign language classes
Yeah
Names, nombrés, my name is very easy.
I took French as well.
You took, oh, Paris-vous-Français?
I also took Spanish, which I learned how to talk a little bit,
but I could never write that down.
I could never do that.
Well, you know, Spanish is like,
in Southern California, everyone knows Spanish
because it's like a lot of...
Oh yeah.
Next to this.
No, I'm just kidding.
No, I'm not actually serious.
There's a lot of Spanish names, like there's a whole bunch of streets here,
our name like Elena, Lucia, Margarita, like, and it's like, there's all these,
there are all the names of these.
BBL, Big Booty Latino.
No, there's not that one.
No, sorry, I'm not that one.
No, PBL Street.
There's Avenue B, but not PBL Street.
There's a lot of Mexicans.
Yes, but I love, the good thing is I'm attracted to Mexicans
and Brazilians.
They should be able to stay for sure.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm really against like deportation
or anything like that.
But I'm also like, I think they should like,
I think there should be more of a naturalization.
Road to it, but you know we had a lot of problems with the border like with people coming from like Jamaica over the Mexican border and coming from like
Europe over the Mexican border of military-aged men that were getting
Like large checks every month and a place to live and it's like what can we get that too?
Who aren't I attracted to I'm not attracted particularly
certain Asians like certain like there's like there's a Korean game
member I knew that was like really like buff and stuff and he was like he was
Oh my god that is in the chat yeah
Dang that I'm not a fan of Ricky Martin or Maynuto. Not really. They're a little he's a little bit too gay
Like I mean, it's like I don't like like the really flamboyant
Mexicans like that that um that who's that guy that does the astrology and he's I think he's a wrestler too
Have you ever seen that guy? He's like blonde. Don't think I've seen that mixture. You haven't seen that guy
doesn't even know I'm talking about who's that guy's
Astrology, I was gonna go no to Gracie Tyson, but then you said he's a wrestler as well
He's like he's like an astrologer and he's like he's like Victor. I forgot his name
But he's like and he's like he looks like a Mexican wrestler
But you know there are gay Mexican wrestlers there's like a gay faction of it
Just like there's kind of a gay faction of American wrestlers, too
Like I mean, I think there would probably be a portion of you know, obviously if it's a profession like some of them are gonna be gay
Ricky Martin's he's he's attractive, but he's like too flamboyant living in a Vida loco. Oh
Okay, that was bad
Um, the thing that is when I come up in, uh, I don't know that I kicked him off him.
I kicked him off like 10 times.
Why'd you kick him out?
Sike, Sike, don't kick off midnight.
Don't kick off this part.
Hey, it's okay.
Okay.
Come on.
I'm gonna, I love you.
Think that is, think that is.
Oh my gosh.
Can you believe that?
You gotta hit, you gotta post the link though.
Again.
Yeah, I know.
I'm sorry.
You have no idea about his personal life.
Oh, what was it? It's like, it's like...
Live in a Vida, look at her.
Yeah. What was his other song?
I believe So Lu.
Yeah.
I fucking know.
He came out a while ago.
Can I imitate Ivana?
Ivana Punchu?
Oh my god, Ivana Punchu.
Or Ivana Trump.
That was not a Russian accent.
That was not a Russian accent right there.
Ivana Trump. I miss this Trump.
How are you doing?
I don't know.
Yvonne in the chat is Russian, though.
We don't know, we don't know.
We're trying to figure it out.
Well, he's a Canadian.
You know, I remember Connie West had this personal trainer
and he actually was like from the,
like the mind control division of the Canadian government.
And he like, hey, your girlfriend's Russian,
your ex is too.
Hey, have you seen my Russian friend?
I like one of my best friend is Russian.
She's got out of prison actually and
She's doing really good now. It's got a job and stuff, but she's really beautiful. We're gonna see her once again
Come on fucker said I got a pee
You got some pee so she and this this is the one that brought me all my cats and stuff like that
and I've known her since like
2009 probably
and
She's cool just she's cool like a
you know pretty wild pretty wild um and she brought me much most of my cats um so where's
her picture and is she is she single no she has a boyfriend like here's picture i'll put on full
Yeah, she's single, perhaps, maybe a little bit.
No, and I made some pictures of us, too.
Like, I did some, you know, I generated some.
Yes, hold on, I'll show you.
Uh-oh.
Where are they?
Come on.
Oh, my cute kitty cat.
Oh, my gosh, there's all the cement I got.
You ever see that?
Well, there's better. Oh, look at this one. Merry Christmas. Wow
Yeah, she's here she's in she was in jail here
You match
I don't think so, I don't think I mean some of them I some of them I well this this one's AI
I mean this is there's an AI on me and then this one's an AI for her
I think she's in this turkey dress unless that's a real real dress, but she also has her
braids
I'm looking Dutch. No. No, these are no she's no this is real
Yeah, I got it for you. Who's asking for it though? I think that is. Oh,
actually, is it actually him? Yeah. Yeah, so it's because you showed him with
braids, man. He don't like that. And I did some pictures here, but let me see.
Oh my god
Yeah, russians are beautiful people, you know, like there's a lot of beauty. Well, you know
Russians are pretty beautiful. They're fucking rude as fuck, but they always sound rude, but I think maybe like harmony
Some are like that. Oh my god
Now you're gonna bitch that I'm up here every other time you always want me to come up
I mean, you know what? This is the first time you've ever won a debate. I can see it
I always do bitch for you to come up here
Now
Drinking coffee or no. Yeah, I got a coffee
Yeah, yeah cock
I heard a fucking psyche was crashing out there like you got to go up there. He's
Half our median you heard psyche was cat who was crushing out what
But I came up here and he wasn't so I'm a little bit a little bit
Shan like a little bit, but she's like actually not like she's actually like really
Good-hearted and well, no, no, I mean, I don't know that it was like kind of like a minimum security prison
Let's get it. Let's serious. Let's get out
Fuck just said dumb dumb dumb or that was that was rude
Where do you want to go loser?
Hang on. I get up open my fucking child. I said hi to loser earlier when I had child
Oh, oh you want to do IRL
Okay, well you can do it by a real loser. Like are you you're in LA? We I don't want it not yet to like me to meet someone
but you're one of the
I wish I could go to Hollywood. I'm pretty much stuck here like I have an e-bike, but it's not even working right now
So I can't really Hollywood's kind of far. It's like a little bit
Did you ever get the the e-bike working? No, like like my I didn't see one part
It's like 20 bucks on Amazon and it's like but my friend knew the part it was the exact one and I don't
He hasn't been back, but I'm gonna try to get it fixed. It's everything else is fine
I think that is like hi. Oh fucking look. He says hi thingy. Yeah. Yeah, I just said hello to
I mean unbanned RG because I do like RG and I don't know why I know you get pissed but Jesus
I know, but I don't like to be vis-shad and like told to apologize to people that I don't need to apologize to because it's like
You don't understand what's been said in the situation the back and forth
So people like I want people to say oh, I need to apologize and like I did something wrong
Well, maybe like, you know, there's apologies on both sides. Oh, but it's like at the end of the day
I don't hate anybody but okay
Well, you see backstage or something is he? No, I just remember that I said I don't
If I did say anything but I mean, I don't believe I really did
We have hey eight into bets George Wallace and I GG ER only one way
Yellow snowman Cali blue 12th stage scat man John concrete layer flavor blasts
Kit to completion daddy Docs Hayden
Familam Anthony 10th stage crystal Marie. Oh my god, Chris and Marie's band. Oh my god
But I keep saying I'm gonna go
Psycho's that's not right. If I unmute you might gonna hear the birds. Is that okay? I'll just meet up
By birds man, isn't like the line but
Yeah, please please. I want to hear the sound of birds. Let's hear
Can't you hear them?
There it is. Did you freshly shave or what's going on? I shaved yesterday. I went out. I went out last night
So I did my you know my head
Just went out to a club locally. Hmm. Watch some music. That's your brand
Yeah, I like light music. I only hate the newest mod. Well, you know, well
Deal with it. Okay, let me see by the way psyche that shirt you're wearing. I think it was last night that button-up shirt
Thank you, I'm so fucking that looks good. Yeah, clumsy on band clumsy was so rude last night
I mean they're all making fun of my music and so I literally
This is like I let you guys on for like five hours
Then I came on played one three-minute song and it's like oh
We're just like they bitch like making fun of me and they say oh that was good
Crushed out they did I don't remember that I remember it because you were you were kicked off at the show at that time
So, so, so, so, so, so, so, so,
I don't know. I mean, it's like I really don't want to like ban people for that long, but
Don't ban them. Don't hide them
Time them out for five minutes. I'm just saying this way they come back at least you know that they come back
You don't know they always come back. No, I'm just saying you don't have to physically go in and hide them
That's that's what I'm saying. I need to check the list every day. I'm making a list checking it twice
Gonna find out.
Gonna figure out who this is.
Famous because of you.
I'm not doing the exact thing.
I said, I would have,
but dental enthusiasts,
why would I fucking care about 200 viewers
if no one's donating?
If no one's, you know,
like why do I care if there's no scrolling me?
I'd rather have 10 viewers that are like cool, right?
And I wouldn't, I would have 200 viewers anyway.
I mean, not even beat or say
I'm gonna make those kind of numbers, please.
Okay, I had five numbers. I had 50 people. I had 50. I had like 80 people last night at the most and I had like at least
25 to 30 people at least and so that was fine
The ten viewers weren't doing any either. Well, that's what you're wrong
But here's what else you're wrong. You're out of this chat about that. So I won less viewer in the chat
Oh, yeah, I'm gonna feel so bad like try to make me feel like hey, my music
You're looking you're looking you're sounding good. Yeah, I'm feeling all right. Who are you talking to?
Well, the North cow was saying horrible things about me yesterday. He's saying I'm a tweaker. He said he said he said
Oh, I've seen most disgusting, you know, homeless people and
No one's worse than psyche eating fries
Oh, that's disrespectful, I wouldn't let that shit slide about you. It's ridiculous. I look good
I wouldn't let it slide. Oh, it's called muckbang
Oh god, that's disgusting. The word is even more disgusting than the action
You want a mukbang? I mean, isn't that word just disgusting just on its own?
Do you know Narkely's make cock rings he he worked for the first cock ring manufacturer. Yeah, yeah
No, I might order I might order a couple. Does he ship international? I don't need to ask him
He's around but you know what he if you work for like the guy who invented them basically in San Francisco
I don't need the guy that invented them to tell him to I can buy them from anyone
If that doesn't matter you want the professional yet. You have a measure by just the fact that they were invented is the good thing
Oh my god, it's what I said come up here. We can go back. I don't
And also midnight was talking serious shit at kates. I got all those free shots of all the shits that she was talking about me
We don't want no drama brother. What do you mean for self use the loser? What do you mean?
Yeah, so we can like don't one there's only one use doesn't matter if it's self or
Somebody else
There's only one you I just fucking I'm banning night like 10 seconds ago and then literally
Yeah, I know I saw the screenshots and oh my god, you know, oh, you know
He's he all he wouldn't worry about when his cat disappeared is going to get a some beer and didn't even look for him
I'm gonna muck baby. You get something that is
Oh, yeah. Oh, it's actually mutt bang in my name in the same sense. I'm sorry. Okay. I saw all those screenshots
Okay, loser now you want to be loser don't start come on. What are you doing?
Sorry
We just hang out
So boys
We got thing that is but as up here, you know
Hey guys, if you want to if you want to like decide who to kick out of your
Dad and who to say you can have your own shows, right? You need the time out. I'll give you one
Don't you have mods brothers, um random
Okay, yeah
Loose asshole, I think I might make a little one. I need a loose ass a little sassel
That's funny come on
That's a funny name
Along but I'll probably unhide you later loser, but you have to like lie
Is that his actual name loser?
Yeah, his name is the loser
Well, but well, you yeah, you already know what's gonna happen. You fucking dumb dumb
That's name
Spank him daddy
Hey yo
I
Just because I just read what Shan wrote and shot
Yeah, that's what happened
We're gonna go to San Francisco, right? Yeah, you don't need to really be like as long as I mean is you'll you'll know who to ban
They're just gonna be like the really
they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they say, they
We're gonna meet some woman at the cashier district and
Whatever the wherever it was turn off the lights and see what happens
He said he's down
We're gonna be in that base thing that is there might be punches thrown
Okay, oh my god
I do that's why she's always like I'm gonna fucking you know, I'm gonna I'm gonna punch you in the face
I'm like, oh, please daddy do it. Do it. God, you're not it. You're not a tender lover. Are you?
Look me I like to be smacked around but you know who else I would never punch a bitch in the face
I punch her in the throat will sass. Oh, yeah, we'll sass or
I don't want to have my trachea broken, but hey, I don't mind having a little smack
it up.
He said he was spitting my mouth, but he said I had to catch it and he was like spit up
in the air.
Oh my god.
Yeah, I did.
I did hammer did say that he would just spit it in the air. I'm not directing your
Donkey on some
Right, but I'm just saying he's not going to spit directly into your mouth is what he said
I will be like a fucking basketball player
All right, that's I mean NFL player first of all second wall. That's very disgusting. It is pretty disgusting
But it gives me
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
Yeah, girl, whatever it is
When I ban Syrax, no, but I'm sure you would make a cock ring for me if you paid it paid you that
So there's NorCal NorCal. Can you make thing that is a cock ring?
You make win one I told him you're like, I'll get you the girth measurement like I don't know it off top my head
I'll have to work on that one
I know she's talking but you said I was a tweaker and then you said you've met like the most disgusting filthy bums
But then I no one's been worse than me eating french fries
Did you say that?
Something like that
I'm pretty sure I heard that yeah
Yeah
It's okay. I forgive you. Norka has a nice hairy chest. Yes from he was on beat as yesterday. Oh my god
He does. I remember one time he came up and when he was on with like I think tiger butterfly and she's like, oh my god
What is that and he was like this is a nice ball head. I just forgive him
Hey, well, you know what just plug your ears or look away or just like and some people do like to hear people eat
Yeah, they have their own channels for that. It's the muckbang channels. Maybe I'm gonna contract some of that audience
Well, then put it in the description then put it in the game title
Okay, look at Sam and his trash
I don't like muckbang and if you had it in the title, I probably wouldn't join so it's good to know
You're concerned? I'm always concerned. NorCal's a simp. Yeah. Don't fucking start, man. Come on, Psych.
Who'd I ban?
I thought you were gonna fucking hide NorCal, no. No, I
Know NorCal since the beginning of my show. I thought you had a moderator in here who did that for you. I
Do and I have a couple loose assholes
And
Yeah, NorCal is cool. Okay thing that is is is better than psyche
Is greater yeah, oh he's bigger. He's a bigger ego. I have a bigger ego. I don't think you have a yeah
Yeah
My eagles not that big you're in zero DM idiot salmon wants to be with psyche
Oh my god, he goes not that big. He wouldn't join this fucking panel if it was I think salmon really is gay
I really do think he's gay. I think he's like I think that is is is better than salmon. Okay, that makes more sense
No one's talking shit about good in the comments really
How does that make you feel?
I feel pretty happy at this point.
I feel pretty good.
Yeah, well it goes.
It's been a while since.
I'm going to get my sneak staff here.
Hey, chop the link.
What the hell?
Drop the link.
Drop the link, brother.
Sam is gayer than me.
I think Sam is gayer than me.
Yeah
Some butt stuff
Cook Tommy Tommy just like a
$10 mess sales $10 benty who wants to get me high and then he was like
And then he's like rolling around his bed in his underwear looking like a big I don't know if he's farting
Oh, it was it was it was really bad and even Sam was like don't do drugs
You can't make
But yeah, I mean I was like, and then like Aldi was like,
and you knew who else was on the show?
Noelle.
That was crazy.
They're incredible live missy.
They're responsible for rap, rock without keys.
Who's he talking about?
I just read that, but who's he talking about?
Primus, Primus, Primus.
Oh, Primus, yeah.
Can you just hold up a cane?
Would you just hold up a cane?
Yeah, my staff, it's my...
Oh.
Oops.
Oh, I love it.
I'll put them on top though.
It was I mean he yeah. Hey, what's up? Happy Sunday to you. I agree. Yeah, I
Larry the guitar snow. I'm having a good morning today. Didn't the drummer just get replaced? Are you ghost?
Yeah, I am
That's good
Guys I'm in trouble now
It's the legend, man, the myth, the legend.
Guess who it is.
What happened?
Oh, Tommy.
Hey, what's up, everybody?
Give me a sec.
I'll get my camera on.
I'm just getting back in the crib here.
Tommy, how are you?
I'm doing good.
I'm feeling great.
I thought I'd come up, have some dialogue, interesting
conversation.
Well, I was I thought it was pretty fun. It was pretty funny, but it's pretty crazy that you was that real fence
Fentanyl you were doing. Oh
That was all stripped. You guys was totally it was I'm a good actor. Okay, I
Would never do I'm so anti-drug it's ridiculous like I hate that shit
Like John Ritter of the physical comedy when you're rolling around the bed. That was pretty funny
Pretty pretty good acting right?
Well, it was good. Yeah, I thought it was real good
So anyway real quick. What's up thing? We'll chop it up with things first and foremost. I don't get
Yeah, man, my March just looking just hanging and living. How you doing Tommy?
I'm good, man. I just wanted to say, you know,
thing I always I don't talk too much, but I always see you on panel you for the most part
you've always seemed like a
You know, real chill guy level headed. Um, grounded, um, intelligent. Um, you know, not no glaives. No, uh, no freak over here. I'm just gonna hold on a minute. Let me cook this up. Uh, thing is, you know, and I'm talking even after the, you know, your, your, uh, alcohol induced rage, which I don't think was much compared to what we see around here.
So you're even with some ciders. I don't know what you drink. You seem pretty, you know, you kind of got a good grasp on things opposed to a lot of people or so, you know, I think now I do have a couple of questions if you don't mind.
So I see kind of what's going on, you know around lately and everything and I do what would like to talk to psyche too
But thing I
Man, I got to say that out of anybody, you know, I'm surprised that you don't you know, you don't do more do diligence
Psychium gonna give a little pass and I'll handle you but I see Brandon Q is now mod didn't donate by the way
But he's your mod
Don't know if it's it's it's a defiance thing, but I'm pretty sure he donated, but I don't have proof, right?
I can't it's a theory, but anyway, and I'm sure a lot of people have said that but thing
You being you know kind of a voice or reason I've seen on a lot of streams
Wouldn't you think this would be something to like yeah, I have you said anything or have you even?
Have spoken to him about the not about him being mod. I this is the first I've heard of that
I don't even see that's crazy. I don't even see him in my chat
So either he's got me blocked or I've got him blocked
But I have talked to psych that yeah
This is not a good character that he would want to have a real well Brandon Q's an absolute faggot
He blocks everyone and he's uh, he's in that. I mean, here's the thing man
Um, just because somebody is an absolute predator doesn't mean that they have a charge, you know, they haven't got caught up, but we, you know, there's enough footage out there of what he said.
There's video of him literally flirting with miners online.
I don't know how much more you would need.
to say, hey, maybe this ain't a good one.
Evidence and stuff like, you know,
the person that told me the most about it was like,
Alexandra and you know, she told me some stuff,
but the person that sent me all the evidence was Tony,
who's my stalker.
And so it's like, and he told me that I need to do.
And so I am defying about it.
And then, you know, I'm also getting all these,
all this shit, all this otherwise shit.
And it's like, I'm just gonna judge people.
I'll let them be in my chat.
I don't care.
I'll talk, I'll even talk to them.
Talk to a serial killer. I don't care. I'm interested. Have you guys seen what my chat's like and what I let go on in my chat?
Yes, I know well it was there and that she's a controversial figure too, right?
Oh, of course, but she doesn't flirt with minors. Um, here's the thing
It's a minor though. She's retarded, right?
No, I'm retarded should I doesn't mean I shouldn't be on panel hold up this real quick
We're kind of speeding through this and I want to keep this real calm let everybody talk
We're not I'm not gonna yell over you
She's done it like she's done it twice it
She did it to me ten times before I even knew who you were and I still let her on
You know who isn't allowed in my chat let alone the panel the one person
Literally brand in Q literally
No, let me talk. Do you smoke fentanyl on a website?
Stop talking over me junk. Well, I wasn't talking first. You're just like already
There's a video of me 31 miners play it play it. Let's see it
Let's see. Dude, I don't know what it is. We've all seen that.
We've all seen it, dude. We've all seen it, dude.
Because you guys see all this shit and then you don't produce anything.
Here's the thing. Here's the thing. I didn't come up here with clips loaded.
I've seen that. No, you can do it. Then do it.
Then do it. Okay. So I'll set it up and we can play it. Then do it. Hey, hey, then do it. Hey, bro. Hey, bro. Hey, when you overdose, bro, I hope you do it on camera.
Yeah, we all live a lot longer than you, bitch. Boy, listen. Oh, yeah. Okay, bro. Listen, dude, you're literally
You've got organ failure, bro. You're broke. You're a bomb. Guess what, bro? I'd make you know that. All that. Yeah. But you know what? I'm not
You know what? I'm not
A pedophile.
No one video of me flirting with a minor.
Let's see it.
We'll click to let me know when I can talk.
It's been playing for the last few days, Jesus.
Everyone's playing right now.
Have you know you're not you're not looking good in all this, okay? I know why
Your shit right by infos out there don't do something. I'll break your neck. I will I will
I will use I would love you to die. Do you know where where show it in psyche? Have you seen the video with a minor?
You know when I can respond to what you're saying. I'm not I'm not gonna yell over this dumb retard
Can I respond now?
Okay, real quick. Do you want to act like reality doesn't exist and that are you gonna say it's AI is that next?
There's nothing that's good. There's nothing to call A.I. because you don't know anything.
There's nothing to call A.I. because you're not going to show nothing.
There's nothing to say. I didn't come up here with anything.
You're not going to show anything. You have nothing, bro.
I came up here to have a conversation. You have no proof, bro.
I didn't come up here to play clips. I came up here to have a conversation.
How about you come up here and show evidence bro and prove I'm a predator, how about you shut everybody up, how about you come up here and you get me banned and you show psyche that I'm a child predator bro, how about you do that?
Dude, he's obviously seen the clips, he already said he's being defiant, he's being defiant because he wants to get back at his chat, he's seen some of what you do for sure.
Maybe not all, but I know you've seen a good piece.
We're starting with a minor, by the way.
Dude, hold on a minute.
You he got the clips as far as I keep saying he got the clips from the number one
A stalker, what yeah, but there's no video me flirting with anybody
Yes, there is
I can tell you more like I'll tell you exactly what I've seen but you got to let me talk
Okay, you see then then show us it then show us it
I have seen you on your little
Show us. Let me know when I can talk. Let me know when I can tell us
I'm not here to play videos and watch a movie with
Shut the fuck up. I'm here to shut you up. Fuck up. I'm here to show a video and proof
Then shut the fuck up and keep my name on here to make sure day up and it's working
Okay, who to screw your whole pay up and it's working
I did come here to watch a little video look how triggered he is he can't even let me talk for five seconds
You can you like you do them or like I do that when people do
Put them back stage. They're like
Something at least
Thought I'll talk but other than that
Brandon Q's an absolute piece of shit. I've seen a lot around here, and I'll tell you one thing about me
I'm a junkie fuck up ten times the hell. I
Love
But you know what I don't love
Fucking around with kids, you know what? I'm not a fucking pdf
So here's the thing bro. I'll be a junkie all day, but I'm good with that
Want to know what I'm not good with?
The things you do you're vertical live streams that aren't even 18 plus where you're on there with miners
There's
Psychi already admitted that he saw some of it being defined towards the stalker in its chat
So you've already failed if people even psyche
Like you did you see me flirting with a minor? No, I saw I saw like a little bit of the vegan
So you didn't see the one where he's with that other weird girl, and they're talking about fucking kids you didn't see that oh
Very interesting where he's with that girl. Let's go fuck it kid. You didn't do that though
Well, yeah, we're just gonna deny deny deny. Is that your game? That's what you do
You've got to be better
You're gonna if you're gonna beat this you got to do better than just deny then show me then show me prove
Because everyone I don't have to show you I've seen it. Everyone has seen it. Why do you think it's
But yet you're trying to convince
So many chatters and viewers don't like you and are like up in arms about this because you're now
If you were if you were in front of me, I'd break your neck and then your glasses not the other way you wouldn't do shit
Bro, I'll get I'll get you a hollow hit of your fucking dealer, bro, and I'll get you a hot shot
You could never
Okay, hey Nazi times for life, so um, yeah
All right, I was waiting for like a response there. Is that all you got Brandon?
You're gonna get me a hot shot. That's your response to talking about fucking kids and flirt with minors on your screen
Hmm
Great guy
Well thing psyche I would honestly
Honestly, do yourself a favor. It's not hard. You have a discord
I'm sure you're possibly in a group chat on IG. If you haven't seen what I'm referring to ask for
I mean, I'll send you a link personally
But um, it's it's not hard to find it's all on YouTube and it's not like this is 10 years ago
So I'm just saying please I'm gonna give you I'm gonna give some grace here
Please within the next 24 to 48 at most
Look into this more than oh, you know, my stalker sent me the thing from two years ago where he was weird with vegan
No, that's not what we're talking about at all
That's just another one some more of his weirdos. Oh, is he not on panel? Thank God. I was like, yeah
I'm afraid to talk. I when is he gonna start raging again, please?
I see I'm giving y'all grace and I'm not just going in on y'all
I'll go in on him, but I wanted to talk to y'all please do not sleep on this this will look
You can say that I it's this isn't coming from a place where I hate thing or I hate psyche
That's that's
on the left side the most important thing is we have to bet and do our part around here
because if you do if you go with what you got cracking it's only going to lead towards a couple
things and i'm not going to speculate i'm sure you know what i'm talking about right
I don't like the guy. I don't want him around. Thank you. Thank you. Hold on. Can I think is this the first time you've said this like
Said it so bluntly. Yes. I've tried breaking it to him in a diplomatic way, but yeah, I don't like the guy
I don't want him around. That's the way I feel. Yeah
Thank you thing because you're being once again. I knew you're level-headed dude. So I just for a minute
I was much like that ain't nobody saying anything and
Thank you say Tommy if you want me to cut him off and me to know the truth
Then say, help me to understand.
I'm not the only one.
What about things?
Say it's just a thing.
Thing doesn't like you either.
Bro, fuck this thing.
I'm all you don't know nothing. You don't know me, but you look like a pedophile
Disgusting man, what did you see? What did you see? What did you see? What did you see?
On fucking women doesn't matter if they're if they're underage you're not be in public you should not be
allowed to speak in public like this, not at all.
We're chillin, we're chillin, we're chillin, we're chillin,
we're chillin, we're chillin, we're chillin, we're chillin,
Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it. Prove it
Ignorant in that they have not looked have not asked for it. Most people don't care
Hey panel panel versus my shit. I mean you're not welcome here
You're on the same platform, so I at least I did a live stream. At least I didn't like you
Know the little
Bro on a kid's website, bro
This is a website
And can easily access and you're on here so when you know on it, bro, my stuff is open and older
You've been on vertical streams that are for everybody not even 18 and older
Getting met with me you're gonna buy vegan man. You try to get
Is that okay to see
Is that true that they saw now they know they saw this I it's proven
Prove it. Did you guys see him try to get in bed with vegan? I did get in bed with her
No, you tried my kisser and I kissed her ten times. Yeah, and she didn't kiss you back
And she did kiss me back. She did kiss me back
No, she left because she she's
Not even
Growing you guys were joking about doing stuff the kids your piece of shit in a promise to you
I'm telling you, bro. Hey, bro. Oh, I know you're a dresser.
Just trust me, you'll find out about me really quick, but
Oh, I don't know.
It's not the dude that can't even hold it.
Yeah, it's not hard.
It's not ours, but, um, you know,
I'm not going to say get to 2448 ASAP.
Ask about the vertical streams the flirting with minors. You will get people that will
It's it's gonna end this is your end of your road Brandon
Do something I am here. I am here to ruin your day and do something
I'm done. I already have. I already have. I got you crying. What brought you around, Brad? I got you screaming and crying because your whole line of defense is broken down. You rely on ignorance and that people have it. Then educate everybody. Then educate everybody. Show the evidence. I have. That's what I'm here to do. Expose me. I'm here to do that and I'm succeeding in it. They knew it. Where is it? Well,
Obviously thing doesn't like you and doesn't want you to answer it.
Enjoy that soul crippling addiction, bro. Enjoy that how much joy that soul crippling addiction, bro. Enjoy it
Enjoy your last
Any of these areas just like you're not a lot you're not allowed to kick it around me
You're not allowed to kick it around here or really quick unless
I
Yeah, I never let you around to call you a bomb to call you a bomb and I'll be that I'll be that but
I'm not a PDF like you don't show up on the kids website some more bro don't show up on the kids website
Look if that's all he's got look you look he literally talked about fucking kids and this is
Wow
But you tried to get in bed with Beacon who smokes meth on stream
You said you were I watched the screen
And she wasn't giving up
YouTube is a kid's website, so why would you talk about why would why would you do all that dude?
Why because I like drugs so I answered your question answer mine
You're just being a hypocrite if that's your defense you're a hypocrite and that's we when you're gonna show some proof
I I do I'm not here to show proof. I'm on a cell phone. I don't have clips loaded up
I didn't even expect you to jump on here and start crying
Isn't slander
Yeah, man, it's a slander and this isn't fake you and you know the blender
So that's why you're so mad listen if someone called me a PDF and and said there's videos
We have proof and it wasn't real. Do you know what I would do? I don't laugh
It's not my show
That's it. Are you part of the norm on a cell phone, right?
In appropriate with minors, that's what you're saying right now. You are denying I don't 100% you have been
I'm asking you to show proof show proof
Yesterday you're so full of shit
What did I do that? What was I doing?
And that's why nobody likes him because he
Nobody likes him either
Who doesn't even have a fucking right to do it
You fucking piece of shit
Fuck you
Watch your mouth bro
You're just a little rascal and you're playing with her
You fuck
Hold on, my name is Thomas Oaks
I live in Spokane, Washington
What's your address?
What you gotta do buddy
It's not hard to find me
You want my address, you know my address
You can write it down or you just acting like a badass, you know write it down
Are you ready? Yeah? I live on
That's right
Balls Avenue my address
If you can't if you don't can't do enough with what you got
He doesn't go live no more
No one gives a fuck about game ball explain your fucking me you jackass
Explain no, I'm asking you you're accusing me of shit. So let's see the proof and then I'll then I'll explain
Let's see the proof bro. Show me some proof
As long as I keep denying it, I'll get away with it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah, you're foolish hitting everybody
Don't even need hey, bro, you don't worry about going to jail for shit that there's no evidence on right
Where's the evidence here's the thing there's a lot of molesters out there that aren't in jail
I'm here to wreck your day. I told you
That's because they're not online
I'm not a
Yeah, they're walking around
He's being defiant right now because of Tony and everything else.
The only people that have station to be a sad man.
Are you going to shut up?
Are you going to get no views?
Bro, you're not even a streamer.
This is retarded.
He's so triggered.
He can't even have a conversation.
You just don't know what you're talking about.
One at a time.
Do you need me to teach you a combo?
Dude, every time I'm in the middle of talking, you start spazzing out.
Spurge.
Come on spaz. You're gonna let me talk cool. So he is literally doing the denied and I deny right psyche will eventually see it
Oh, you're a crash elbow. That's cool. I could be well. I could I could be long but psyche will eventually come around
100%
Clumsy
Disgusting behavior if you want to play some of clumsy's stream go ahead. I don't know how
Evidence you know he was arrested for a QZ of abusing a son, right, you know
Now play it
The video doesn't matter because of the person who is presenting it right notice this psych play it play it
It's no I'm saying play it, it's what I'm saying right now, play it, play it, play it, play the videos, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it, play it,
That's not ignorant educate them educate them then doesn't look like it that's very good. Hey Brandon
It's the same people and Sam ends and they have shot and they hate me because I went over there and talk shit to them
It's because they're little favorite powers. Oh, you don't think that I haven't done that. Oh my god
You think that I haven't done that? This is all the same people I haven't done that. Every single person in there should be a chap.
Dude, they won't even come around anywhere I am because I've already dealt with them, dude.
You're next
Hey Tommy, hey Tommy, I'm gonna need to see some evidence, bro
Everybody's seen this shit
That you haven't seen any of the stuff. What did you see? What did you see? What did you see?
Hold on
Notice how he's saying notice how he's saying what have you seen? What have you seen?
You have not seen what everybody in chat has been talking about
No, they're saying him all that bullshit in discord bro. There's nothing
They already send it ultimate. No, he only watched a little bit of it and it came from somebody he doesn't like so he's not taking it serious
If that's what he needs if he needs more that's easier
Show a video of me being inappropriate with a minor bro. Show a video of me being inappropriate with a minor. I'll wait
I'll wait. He will see it the day when west today. What time?
What time what time do you shut up for a second so we can get it done? Hey chat
For one, nobody wants to for one. I'm just gonna say this not many people have this saved because of what you're doing
If not, I will get you put backstage. Let me say this you literally are just so fucking you all you do is repeat yourself, dude
There's so much evidence so much, but how many regular channels when you can show it hold on
Hold on. How many people want to have videos of some spas being inappropriate with underage girls on their personal cell phone?
Not me. I don't have anything like that because it's weird. Why would I but
Now since it doesn't exist, it's because it doesn't exist. Look what i'm gonna do. Hey chat
I know a lot of you guys are on discords and some of you in psyches
Send them exactly what we're talking about. Get them what he needs
Get him like, hold on, get him like, get psyche, what he means to see.
So we don't have to deal with this PDF anymore.
All right.
We can get rid of this promo faggot today, right now, actually.
Get it over to them.
Do it.
I don't have this.
I don't.
He'd shit like that on my phone or computer, but people don't like you and they got files
They do have it archived and it will get the psyche
You just said nobody wanted
Spun the corner on you and said yeah, you're full of shit. He doesn't you don't know me. You don't know
Man and I've seen it myself
So I know you're full of shit man.
What did you see?
That's crazy work work help literally Brandon Q makes LD look like a cool dude
That's how he's a good man. LD's a good man. No, of course you would say that of course
I bet that I'm sure you I'm sure you feel that way. I'm sure that he's a very good man
I'm sure he's one of the reasons you came over here. So the thing is but
Somebody clip that by the way, but anyway
So I already see
There's some people at work who do avid archive. There's PI read chat. It's not hard psyche
I'm pretty sure by the end of today if not the afternoon you're gonna have
What you need to personally see thing has seen enough
I've seen enough chat has seen enough the people have spoken and you're done. You little chill mode
And do something about it and do something about it. Hey, guess what? I'm gonna be
I already have I'm doing it right now
I'm gonna be here every day, bro. I'm gonna start dating cycle. I'm glad you think that you want to bet on that
Yeah, yeah, I will
That's where you're concerned with that. You you just want to fucking troll everyone
You don't give a shit about fucking being here, right? You just want to be an ass
Shit
No, no, you're just a sex pest and a little faggot like that's all you is dude
You're just a fucking danger to anybody who's not 18 anything under 18 is a huge danger around you
animal children
Kills kids destroys you promote fentanyl you promote fentanyl use
How are we kidding? You're promoting a poison. You promote poison.
I bet you sell fennel. I bet you sell fennel.
Let's do all he can do is project and deflect
Nobody
No, you will you've I've definitely seen you promote math. So we want to talk about it
I promoted me. How did I literally on screens? You literally on your screen said you're gonna buy vegan math to get
Around you and that you love
You think that has your screams on my computer. Do you think I like care about you like that people like you?
I do everything I can to forget exist
But yeah, you're here. Do you ask what I'm gonna do about it? You ask what I'm gonna do about it
Well, I'm here and I've done something about it my question. Yeah, but not anything. You haven't showed anything
My question is you know, I have all you've done is slander me all you've done is commit a crime that slander
I can call your police station right now and get you arrested for this.
Huntsley, he slandered me.
Except it's not slander.
It's real life.
It is.
No, it's slander.
You can't slander.
Yeah, it is real life.
You agree.
Finally.
It's real life and you're mad about it.
Real life slander.
That's why you're buying.
Real life pedophile.
You.
Shut up, bro.
You smoke fentanyl on a kid's website, bro.
Shut the hell up.
Yeah, you promote poison imagine the dystopian world where some dude is promoting fentanyl on the kids website
What your boys and buddy
Comes on YouTube or kids watch Robots videos and shit
Are a restricted
and they're 18 plus
and this shit is not
that's against TOS
put it in 18 and you can promote fentanyl
it doesn't say you put it 18 plus
and you can promote fentanyl to kids bro
that's not how it works
that's against TOS
for that reason
that's against TOS for that reason
because kids could be on platforms
And you should be on vertical streams on it on this platform. That's for kids flirting with minors. What's worse?
I would say that never did with mine never did and is a little bit worse than doing with some substance
That everybody never did that never did that but hey start meeting what you did
so everybody
but that's how they are. They leave their needles at the parks, they smoke fentanyl in front of schools, all that shit. They don't give a fuck. They shit in your yard. You're the piece of shit, bro.
All you can do is deflect and say everything. You just want to get all this heat off of you, on the me, on the thing, whoever else you can, anything to get it off you.
Don't hit your foil, bro. Don't hit your foil hard. Hopefully that's the one.
Go hit that shit, huh? Oh, bro. Hit that shit hit it hit it hit that shit, bro
Be a man, dude. You okay? Are you okay?
Hit that shit bro. Go hit the foil. Are you okay?
why is because are you getting like
are you getting cravings?
are you getting cravings right now?
someone did like
you getting cravings right now?
you squirming around getting cravings
like oh I wish I had some
god damn it
I'll just fucking get this bag
because I'm branding you
that is literally you
you've literally said that
Yeah, you have never told some kids you win that girl. Let's go fuck kids. Yeah
Like it's all cute and funny. You're a POS
The only people who are gonna like want to hang out with you are other weirdos other chomo faggots
That's all your that's the company for the rest of your life like that one weird girl you had around another chomo faggots
That's all you're gonna have
Ever not even vegan wanted to fuck with you that sad sad work
Yeah, she spent the night at your house, but you still didn't hit
how's that feel like no she drove 24 hours to get to was up she was stepping the mountain how does it feel
how does it feel going through all that trouble and i don't care i got better pussy there was no trouble
she i just said come over and she came over i didn't have to do nothing what did i have to do i do
i didn't have to do i do just getting better
a dude that's getting better pussy does not act like how you have acted bro i literally
have a final stroke right now you're literally hooked up with chicks that i've known bro literally
chicks that i've known for years i've hit them all the time yeah you're a big yeah like there's a channel
that's called branding q loves kids that fucking has a video of him doing all this fucking shit with
minors okay if you want to have it on there you see why nobody wants to like watch it like play it
can I play it then play it can you shut up for 10 seconds
what's I see what things I said you see why nobody wants to like
have to dig this up and go to these channels and get these clips because it's
fucking because it's fucking disgusting and he wants you to play it
he's playing it literally yeah I do want you to play it right I do I do want
I do want you to play it I do
That's why I want you to play a lot to prove that you're full of shit. All right, let's go
Because that's
Shit out there and be like oh look here it is
But then they don't want to show it because
I know what channel that is actually there's way worse. There's way
Channel trust me. I've already made that channel psyche will psyche will get
What is necessary in a bet and he will send them right now, I'll send him $20, brother play it.
He will say, I have seen enough.
Spike, take this into account, okay?
This is just the channel that's on YouTube, okay?
YouTube is worse on rumble, okay?
There's way worse on rumble.
I
Was watching last night on these two I was watching the videos
For you fucking creeping on kids you fucking pieces shit
Why you lying this is screaming in line
Can I talk to psyche without being interrupted please things been can have a convo. He's not doing this weird like spaz
Triggered I'm caught typing psyche. Are you taking it? Do you care about any of this and real question?
Are you taking this into account?
Right, I mean it's like if it's like
It sounds bad. I mean it's like but
I mean, so how are you gonna feel when you personally see what everyone else has that they've said I've seen enough
No, he has not you need to just be quiet brain and I'm talking to psyche
Listen psyche, I'm giving you right mean you don't get along at all
Is that fair to say we don't on record or as a our history?
We don't necessarily fuck with each other a bunch. You don't hang out on my channel
I don't I rarely might stop by and you know like this come by and have some dialogue
I
Literally I'm trying to give you grace to wear a big part of me. Just don't give a fuck
Okay, I
Yeah, I'm not saying you need to kick him demod him. Well, I am saying that you should do all that right now
But I'm telling you man. You don't seem like you really fucking care
Well, I'll say that you're gonna kick me. No, I don't I'm just used to because you're talking you're talking like, you know
Genuinely and not like yelling at me. Yeah, I'm not here to troll you
I am not here to troll you call you names or fuck to dig into your background
Well, I'm not here for that. I'm here to do what needs to be done and we're doing it and he's very mad about it
He's very mad about it
I mean, maybe that's, but maybe the part of it is like, you know, I'll let people like psych,
you know, he's not going to stick around. You know, he's just here to fuck things up. You know
that, right? Exactly. And he does this everywhere. But psych, you won't listen. And trust me,
I don't listen to people either. I do what I want. I don't like being told what to do. If I feel like
if i feel like i'm being pulled what to do i'll probably do the opposite but this is one of
those few situations where you need to really whatever you got to do do it do it quick
Because we have to like we have to like we're setting the bar real low and Brandon don't give a fuck about any of this
He's literally just looking for a place to hang out because he's not allowed anywhere else
He's not even allowed on my panel
Bro this side is sad bro like this shit's a
And in the chat doing nasty porno's making bestiality videos
And then Lou Karris, who cares about that?
Did anybody else
She's saying I'm in great VP that never happened, bro, that's a lie
The way you were the way you were like she didn't ask her a kiss
She didn't come give you a kiss you were hover hovering over her in your
Trying to get in the van kissing her all over the place to the
Point to where she had to leave. I'd say there was no assault. There was no assault. There was no assault, girl. That's not what she left.
She left because she said I was acting like Nick.
She was afraid, probably, that if she just said the wrong thing, you might have killed her or raped her.
Honestly, that's how I would feel.
I'd be like, I'd better get out of here.
But Green said it's a lie. That's why he wouldn't take you serious, huh?
I'd better say whatever I got to do to get it. I'd better say I'd better say I'd better say whatever I got to do to get it.
Why did I go to jail? Why did she defend me? Why did she defend me?
Why did she defend me? Why did she defend me?
I'll answer your question if you shut the fuck up you tromophagic.
Shut up, you fucking punk fucking. So here's the thing. I think you report me a trauma
Do you know how many people you know how many people you know how many people get assaulted great
Everything be all this dude. I just know I don't happen to me the other
I think she happened to me the other day and I could call the cops I could have
Yes
Even when it's really really serious a lot of the time people don't go to the police
Is that what happened?
What happened bro when you're shouting your answer
Everybody who gets does everybody who gets sexually assaulted get go get charges and go to jail
As soon as they commit the crime they're buying
The people saw it was on video and thousand the people saw right
Yeah, but the victim, the victim, the victim, the victim, the coke laughing isn't working because the victim has to go, the victim has to go report it.
He's not
Anybody can call the police and say oh, I just saw this happen the victim has to go and report it everybody knows that
No, what the type of prime?
Okay, so they don't need the witness to say that that wasn't consensual. I didn't want that they totally
Show your face around yeah, how do you have no shame?
and what are you going to be doing on his camera
because Pomsite Q ain't a thing
I would move to another country
I would be so ashamed that people would
fucking know my history, oh my god
I don't want them in my country, I don't want them in my
planning
to do something about it bro
this late buddy
I don't have to do anything
yeah you do
the lords already got that handled brother man
How the good Lord man, why am I doing that handle? Why am I doing better than all of you?
Oh, you're doing so good, and I'm so jealous dude. I
We all wish that we were you we all want to be
This is fucking
So I beside and blowing you up prove it prove it
Prove it
Prove it. Oh, so now it's oh, but you don't want to prove your shit. Oh, but no you were doing the same thing to me
But like look at yeah, who cares about I who cares about this Poseidon we're talking about something a lot worse
Your crimes against humanity. That's what
I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't know why I don't
I'm a hunter, man. There we go. I agree
You absolutely are and you won't be around long. This is
Enjoy your last day week, whatever it is around here. I'm just happy
I'm happy I can go back
Hey, God bless
Enjoy that
I'm gonna be smoking on you bro
Every day, bro
Well, if that's how it is, that's how it is, you know smoke my ashes smoke them up put them in the pookie pipe
Hit it up
Go hit that foil Tommy
Don't hit that foil. It's waiting for you, bro. I'm against drugs. I don't promote. I don't promote
Drug use now, I don't promote drugs
Go take a look drugs. Go take a look. I don't do drugs. No, listen. Just like you're just like your Tomo faggot shit
Yeah, you that doesn't happen that never happened. I don't do drugs either. I've never touched a drug
I don't promote it. I don't do it. I've never done a fire sale. I'm not cool with any of that
I've never done it. And if I have somebody prove it prove it
Hey, it's not real prove it
Just that how much do they pay you for the be how you want to talk about anything else other than what we're talking about
No, it's bitches. She's like a fucking chat going insane
The chat hate with a lot of people hate you God and do something about it then do something about it
I don't have to do do some I don't have to you're already like you're already a withered broken human
I don't got to do shit to you when there's a little affidue
Make your life miserable
I'm gonna do nothing and I succeeded this on final calling me with it
Well
My voice may be with you, but my soul isn't with her. I'll be a
Junkie all day before I'm gonna be a Tromo, dude. Sorry. You are a
Tromo. It's not hidden. It's not so hard about it. I think
you're trying to deflect from yourself, bro. And notice how
you just called me that. I don't give a fuck because it's
not okay. What about your homie Zeya and salmon?
I'm not friends with Zeya or Section 8.
Do you not realize that we're on that panel and talk?
I'm not going to talk chat nose and they see me put it on.
They see me do the same thing to Zeya that I'm doing to you right now.
Why'd you abuse your mom?
Someone's telling me that you've abused your mom, I heard.
I
Taken my mom out the lunch is abusing her is that what you're talking about
Because that's like
What were you doing? You're you're using a card or what? Well, you know, how did I you tell me?
Financial abuse or what I don't know what you're even talking about
It's not real so I don't care you see how that works
This is uh, bro, no, it is sad you're very sad
the
show proof
Brandon, I've already done what I gotta do.
That's all you got.
What do you do find there's somebody behind the screen
Want to know what I did I watched somebody else a bunch of clips in screens of you doing the worst of the worst
Stuff I really don't even want to mention. I don't want to talk about what nobody does like what are you think?
I want to be here. You think I want to be here talking about the weird crap you do on the internet
You know, I'm obviously here fucking tossing you and I'm literally ripping you a brand-new fucking hole, bro
There's nothing you can do. I'm giving you a second pussy
And you're fucked. There's nothing you can do about it
Scream
Go hit that foil
It's that foil bro. He's just gonna repeat himself
Go hit that foil. Go hit it.
When they get to repeating themselves, it gets sad.
Go hit that foil, bro.
I'm happy I could come up here today.
Educate have a conversation with thing your chomo piece of shit and just enjoy your last little bit of time around here
I got a couple more words for psyche before I bounce whenever you would like
But I don't want to be on panel with this guy anymore
I've done what about I think the most I can do here, but I do got a couple more words for psyche thing
Thank you for having a brain and using it. I guess it's like not hard. This isn't rocket science situation
I would hope not. If it is, then I don't want to be a part of this world no more, bro.
And that kind of ties back to the last days, bro. You're not gonna live long. You're not gonna
live long. These are your last days, bro. Enjoy it. Well, then so be it. So be it. Yeah, good. So
Okay, keep repeating yourself. It's hitting hard. Okay. You hurt my feelings or
You want to talk to Tommy?
OK, psyche's back.
So I think I've done the most of what I can do here.
Psyche, I know that I kind of see what you're kind of trying to do.
I know you're trying to be maybe you feel like you're being diplomatic, democratic.
Maybe this is how you do your due diligence.
But if you were going to fuck around with this shit,
I mean, I'll personally have no choice but to just.
feel about the worst and I don't want to have to have this shouldn't be a thing that takes a month
year at all this isn't rocket science I don't know what you think I don't care
what you've seen if you psyche if you're not kind of able to like say this is
this some bullshit and I should not have this dude around this dudes you think
LG's kind of like got some got some shady shit in his past this dude has got
And I don't want to be on this panel with them any longer, so fuck you Brandon and Psyche, I really man, I don't want to leave, I don't want to be too harsh either.
But I don't feel like it. I don't feel like you're taking it serious dude. It's just another day for you
I mean from with it. I mean, it's like I've seen like a lot of people
Accused of a lot of stuff and like, you know, I understand that it's like
Yeah, and I'm sure I'm sure that the whole chat is just
Your whole viewership other than the ignorant people once again Brandon relies on your ignorance
Everybody's wrong. We just listen
We just all are jealous of Brandon and he mobs everybody so hard.
We just don't want them around.
That's what it is, right?
That is what it is.
Hmm.
That's what they say.
Look, I explain it.
Look, is that what it is?
He can't look.
He's one thing of his own mouth.
That is what it is.
Other than trying to join my panel and chat.
I. Other than that.
That's the most I ever want us and like I said, I don't even think I have us
He's literally the only person and that says a lot. I let some pretty
Questionable people around my chat, but no chomo faggots
okay, and
If you I'm not gonna call you a PDF
Everything in your power
I met I met him the other day. I haven't received any money from him. I haven't I haven't benefited in any way and that's fine
I have no proof on that like you know what I group on
Bad I want him to like reveal himself, you know, and it's like so, you know, you're gonna wait
You're gonna wait until it's the last minute or maybe until you
Finally watched it after everybody's beg you to you're not taking this seriously watch watch watch watch watch what hey Tommy watch what I
Bullshit
Yeah
You're not gonna be proactive at all you're just gonna see
Just hit the fan and that's it
No, I'll look into it. Yeah, is this it? I'll look into it at some point. Yeah, it's pretty wack dude
Pretty wack. Oh, I'm not at my chat. So I'm gonna do this
Okay, thanks for talking to me on the show what major point I said thanks for being on the show you made your point and
dude
It's gotta be a red flag bro the scene bro like
and you're twisting things bro
you're twisting things bro
unbanned the loser
or unhide him whatever you did
okay
he's been hidden for a while now
like an exaggeration
just jen is saying that i'm on video
raping somebody bro that never happened
and then they wonder why people don't take shit seriously dude
like
he's on video raping vp
bro go ask vp
she'll literally say i did nothing wrong
It was all it was on video like how are you gonna lie like that man like oh my god do that
That's on another level bro, so even you I say man. Oh my god psych. Are you on hiding a loser?
Yeah, right now. Okay. I'm gonna drop. All right. I leave it up to you
Do the right thing boy. I have a screenshot agenda. You said great. You said great. You're all he great VP
Have a screenshot it bro
Okay, loser. I got you. Okay. Let me see if there's anybody else
Nope and even molesting that didn't happen either dude. What the fuck that's fine. You know I can have you charged I
Could contact the police dude
That's a crime, bro. That's literally a crime dude lying and saying all this dude raped some chick on video and
Then it turns out that that's false bro. You committed a crime
It's called slander
Okay, oh and then it's because you didn't get a chance to do it
What is this thought please oh minecraft oh we we know you were gonna you were thinking about it. What the fuck?
That's insane dude, oh my gosh
My gosh
Yeah, okay, I might be oh wow. Well, you know what they're like, I mean crystal Marie was on last night saying you know talking about
You know, big, you know mutilating and torturing and
It's like just like going like
Things way, it's just like we're like and it's like what like no one's gonna say anything about that like what would she say?
She wanted to mutilate me or who?
She said she said oh something about like, you know, you need you need like
You know like razor under eyes under your eyes. So you think people like I don't know
I just like she was just going saying way off things and you should be killed. You should die
And so
Right. Yeah, they do all do crazy things, bro
right
And what I know is a lot of these people have weird funky charges, bro, and I'm dying. I don't
Right, I mean it's like if somebody well, there's like video evidence of something
It doesn't I don't think it matters if there's like the victim comes forward or not
There's something on video of like, you know, some crime being committed
I think that they can prosecute if they you know, there's actually something but I that's why nobody nobody takes them seriously
Because look just Jan is lying saying that I molested VP on video, bro
Like come on, dude. I was showing the video last night, bro
All I do is stand next to her bro. What the fuck dude? That's not assault, bro
Like that's exaggeration, bro. I like that should never be tolerated. That should be
like
You don't put you don't put that shit on people's name. You know what I mean? You don't lie about people like that, bro
Yeah, like if you do you've been here playing dirty, bro. You know what I mean?
I mean at least if like a very serious things are being
Leveled I think someone has the right to
I don't understand like this whole like, oh, let's like, but you know, um, I mean and then they call it deflection blog when I say prove it and they go always deflecting, no, I'm asking you to prove it.
Yeah, I mean, and I brought up like salmon was like, oh, what about Brandon too?
Yeah, I was like, well, you know, aren't you friends with you know, say it was similar like stuff said about him
And I'm not saying anything. I'm not making any accusations about somebody. I'm saying there's controversial people. Why is it like?
Yeah, Santa for different people and it's like it they could be shocked about this
But then it's like oh, but then it's like and it's like I don't know
It's just kind of it's because there's a group of people that hate that better like
Against IP to streamers bro and want to fuck with them and sabotage them get their channels deleted
That's what a lot of those people that came from that panel verse or people like that, bro
Sandman and all those people do that's basically like
Yeah, they're all it's kind of like the same group, bro
I think I'm just giving him like free content and and so I'm just gonna wrap it up right now, but you know
I just who all that did that that's a lead strike. I'm good fuck that is
You know, I don't I don't know I'm I just I think we had it was interesting
At least that was at least it's a good conversation to have I could get off and you could stay on
They'll probably stop string or whatever you leeching. You know what I mean, but I didn't get I got shit to do bro
You don't know. Yeah, well, but thank you for coming on and and you know, I just at least when I give everyone a chance to
To talk and it was maybe a good conversation and and maybe
Yeah, it's good, you know, it's good when you know an hour or two hours go by and it's like and it's just accusations
You know what I mean?
if she was real like you I don't think she would be going back and forth this
long right like come on dude like but all right bro I'm out of here bro I
appreciate you for letting me speak okay and thank you bro okay so wow well
that was interesting conversation
I mean, I like I said it into like true crime and like the minds of
Different types of people and I'd like to get to kind of understand
What's going on psychologically sometimes and so and sometimes it's better like the less I know the better because say people seem to be very
Bandwagon kind of on some stuff. So yeah, so
Right and he's putting up things. Oh, you know, I mean the trolls are gonna jump on on this
And I know some people are genuine, but it's pretty guys
No, it's really difficult to like tell the difference sometimes between like someone
being genuine about
You know, oh, we're trying to help you but as worse like just trying to fucking jump on me and fucking bully me and
you know
Just oh my god, there's just a store jacket on me, too. And so, you know, I mean
What I mean, he's playing this episode on his show is that is that so it's in a way. He's platforming it too
I mean, I don't understand so
Is that a double standard like the thing we care everyone's like all like oh so oh my gosh question the pearls over there
About this, but it's like I'm just fucking letting someone speak. I mean he's not fucking in a in a live
studio audience, you know, it's
It's over the phone on YouTube
If anyone can ever speak again, it's like, you know, might as well be, you know, on YouTube
so
Anyhow, so let me see
Yeah, let's see. Okay, so think
Well, I think that is I mean, I mean, I think so but it's like
But if it ever goes away, then it's already there.
Even when he said one thing in the chat,
it's just as bad as it is now.
I mean, it's like, so what?
So what?
It's like, so, okay.
Well, then, what, is everyone on the panel associate?
I mean, it's like, I mean,
is everyone has so Cuckoo for Cocoa Puffs.
Now he's threatening me.
Oh, he is?
Oh, he's threatening me now.
And he's playing my content and he's threatening me.
Okay, I'll be right back.
Here, I'll put them.
Maybe I'll stop playing if I fun on something. Yeah
You are not dragging
You are cargo
Something else has hands on the wheel.
And it knows your name.
your bloodstream signing all your thoughts
smiling in the mirror while your real self rots
polite little prisoner trained to obey
you call it being good but you're decaying that way
you swallow every instinct
fire your teeth down smooth
call it self-control but you just removed your proof
you had claws, you had fire, you had something divine
now you apologize for crossing your own line
call John whispered from the grave
make the dark conscious or it digs your cave
but you muted the message
sanitize the pain
pretending it's you. Take back the throne, reclaim the room, turn your shadow from a cage,
into a weaponized gloom.
You built a mask so perfect even you forgot, polished every angle till your soul got caught.
They don't love you, they love the role you placed and an ovation for a ghost in a display.
You fake is a fracturing you you feel that hollowness that echo in space that's your real self
Now pretending it's you, take back the throne, reclaim the room, turn your saddle from a cage
Into a weaponized bloom
Everything you hate is a mirror
Every trigger gets clearer
Arrogance, that's your buried crown
Laziness, that's burnout drown
Jealousy maps where your hunger lives
Raid shows what your silence gives
Your enemies are blueprints in disguise
Read them right, you weaponized.
Mask and permission to exist as a man
The moment you stop apologizing for a breath
Is the moment your presence starts to fire in jail
Talk to your moves like they're sitting across
Negotiate storms instead of taking the loss
That voicing your chest isn't random or fade
It's a signal
And once you're whole, reality starts bending around you.